[
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you cross a snowman and a dog?",
    "answer": "Frostbite."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Santa go to music school?",
    "answer": "So he could improve his \"wrap\" skills."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a greedy elf?",
    "answer": "Elfish."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the Christmas tree go to the barber?",
    "answer": "It needed a trim."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get when you cross a bell with a skunk?",
    "answer": "Jingle smells."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you eat Christmas decorations?",
    "answer": "Tinsilitis."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the elf put his bed into the fireplace?",
    "answer": "He wanted to sleep like a log."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a snowman with a six-pack?",
    "answer": "An abdominal snowman."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a cat on the beach at Christmas time?",
    "answer": "Sandy Claws."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you cross a Christmas tree with an apple?",
    "answer": "A pine-apple."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the Christmas lights go to school?",
    "answer": "They wanted to be brighter."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a snowman party?",
    "answer": "A snowball."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Santa bring a ladder to the bar?",
    "answer": "He heard the drinks were on the house."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the Christmas ornament go to the doctor?",
    "answer": "It was feeling a bit off-color."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a snowman with a temper tantrum?",
    "answer": "A meltdown."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the elf go to school?",
    "answer": "To learn the elf-abet."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you cross a snowman and a vampire?",
    "answer": "Frostbite."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a reindeer with bad manners?",
    "answer": "Rude-olph."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the gingerbread man go to the doctor?",
    "answer": "He was feeling crumby."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a snowman with a sunburn?",
    "answer": "A puddle."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Santa go to the beach?",
    "answer": "To be a \"sandy\" Claus."
  },
  {
    "question": "How do snowmen travel around?",
    "answer": "By riding an \"icicle.\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get when you mix a snowman with a baker?",
    "answer": "Frosting."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why don’t Christmas trees sew?",
    "answer": "They always drop their needles."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call an old snowman?",
    "answer": "Water."
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s Santa’s favorite kind of music?",
    "answer": "Wrap music."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you cross an iPad and a Christmas tree?",
    "answer": "A pine-apple."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did one snowman say to the other snowman?",
    "answer": "\"Do you smell carrots?\""
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the turkey join the band?",
    "answer": "Because it had the drumsticks."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does a snowman get around?",
    "answer": "By riding a snowmobile."
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s a sheep’s favorite Christmas song?",
    "answer": "\"Fleece Navidad.\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of photos do elves take?",
    "answer": "(S)elfies."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do snowmen eat for breakfast?",
    "answer": "Frosted flakes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call Santa’s little helpers?",
    "answer": "Subordinate clauses."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a shark that delivers presents?",
    "answer": "Santa Jaws."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the reindeer say before telling a joke?",
    "answer": "\"This one’s going to sleigh you.\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the Santa say before telling a joke?",
    "answer": "\"This one’s going to sleigh you.\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a Christmas wreath made of $100 bills?",
    "answer": "Aretha Franklin."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Santa keep his suits wrinkle-free?",
    "answer": "He uses Claus-et space."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Santa eat for breakfast?",
    "answer": "Ho-ho-ho-tcakes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of cars do elves drive?",
    "answer": "Toy-otas."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Frosty get around on Christmas?",
    "answer": "By riding a snowdrift."
  },
  {
    "question": "What wears a red suit and goes \"Oh, oh, oh\"?",
    "answer": "Santa walking backwards."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a reindeer with no eyes?",
    "answer": "No-eye-deer."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you cross Santa with a detective?",
    "answer": "Santa Clues."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Santa go down the chimney on Christmas Eve?",
    "answer": "Because it \"soots\" him."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Santa get stuck in the chimney?",
    "answer": "He was Claus-trophobic."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Santa go down the chimney at the bakery?",
    "answer": "Because it was a piece of cake."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Santa use to clean the chimney?",
    "answer": "Santa-tizer."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do snowmen like to do on the weekend?",
    "answer": "Chill out."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do elves do after school?",
    "answer": "Their gnome work."
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the difference between Santa’s reindeer and a knight?",
    "answer": "One slays the dragon, and the other’s draggin’ the sleigh."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was Santa’s little helper depressed?",
    "answer": "Because he had low elf esteem."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the cow say on Christmas morning?",
    "answer": "Mooooey Christmas."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do monkeys sing at Christmas?",
    "answer": "Jungle bells, jungle bells."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you sing at a snowman’s birthday party?",
    "answer": "Freeze a jolly good fellow."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Santa have three gardens?",
    "answer": "So he can hoe hoe hoe."
  },
  {
    "question": "When does Christmas come before Thanksgiving?",
    "answer": "In the dictionary."
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the difference between the Christmas alphabet and the ordinary alphabet?",
    "answer": "The Christmas one has no L (noel)."
  },
  {
    "question": "What carol is most often heard in the dessert?",
    "answer": "Camel ye faithful."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if Santa goes down the chimney when the fire is lit?",
    "answer": "Krisp Kringle."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are turkeys smarter than chickens?",
    "answer": "Ever heard of Kentucky Fried Turkey?."
  },
  {
    "question": "What often falls at the North Pole but never gets hurt?",
    "answer": "Snow."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is Santa so good at karate?",
    "answer": "Because he has a black belt."
  },
  {
    "question": "How much did Santa pay for his sleigh?",
    "answer": "Nothing, it was on the house."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do fish sing when Santa comes?",
    "answer": "Christmas Corals."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the reindeer say when he saw an elf?",
    "answer": "Nothing, reindeer can’t talk."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which elf was the best singer?",
    "answer": "ELFis Presley."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Santa take pictures?",
    "answer": "With his North Pole-aroid."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is invisible and smells like milk and cookies?",
    "answer": "Santa’s burps."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Santa put on his head when he has a headache?",
    "answer": "A polar ice cap."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Santa say when Mrs. Claus asked about the weather?",
    "answer": "Looks like rain, dear."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is never hungry at Christmas?",
    "answer": "The turkey - he's always stuffed."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Santa use to measure?",
    "answer": "Santameters."
  },
  {
    "question": "What should you give your parents at Christmas?",
    "answer": "A list of what you want."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do snowmen take when the sun gets too hot?",
    "answer": "A chill pill."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did one snowman say to another snowman?",
    "answer": "You’re cool."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of bug hates Christmas?",
    "answer": "A humbug."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Christmas Day end?",
    "answer": "With the letter Y."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the turkey cross the road?",
    "answer": "Because it was the chicken’s day off."
  },
  {
    "question": "When is a boat just like snow?",
    "answer": "When it’s adrift."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best Christmas present in the world?",
    "answer": "A broken drum, you just can’t beat it."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who delivers presents to cats?",
    "answer": "Santa Paws."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it getting harder to buy Advent calendars?",
    "answer": "Their days are numbered."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of motorbike does Santa ride?",
    "answer": "A Holly Davidson."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do angry mice send to each other at Christmas?",
    "answer": "Cross-mouse cards."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Adam say the day before Christmas?",
    "answer": "\"It’s Christmas, Eve.\""
  },
  {
    "question": "Why don't you ever see Santa in a public hospital?",
    "answer": "Because he has private elf care."
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s a child’s favorite king at Christmas?",
    "answer": "A stoc-king."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get if you cross Santa with a duck?",
    "answer": "A Christmas Quacker."
  },
  {
    "question": "What happened to the man who stole an Advent Calendar?",
    "answer": "He got 25 days."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was the snowman looking through the carrots?",
    "answer": "He was picking his nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call buying a piano for the holidays?",
    "answer": "Christmas Chopin."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the beaver say to the Christmas Tree?",
    "answer": "Nice gnawing you."
  },
  {
    "question": "What athlete is warmest in winter?",
    "answer": "A long jumper."
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of key do you need for a Nativity play?",
    "answer": "A don-key."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do snowmen wear on their heads?",
    "answer": "Ice caps."
  },
  {
    "question": "How do elves get to the top floor of Santa’s workshop?",
    "answer": "They use the elfelator."
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Santa describe the elf who refused to take a bath?",
    "answer": "He’s elfully smelly."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do sheep say to each other at Christmas?",
    "answer": "Merry Christmas to ewe."
  },
  {
    "question": "What color Christmas candle burns longer, a red candle or a green candle?",
    "answer": "Neither – candles always burn shorter."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Christmas carol do parents like the most?",
    "answer": "Silent Night."
  },
  {
    "question": "What goes ho-ho whoosh, ho-ho whoosh?",
    "answer": "Santa caught in a revolving door."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Santa do in his garden?",
    "answer": "He hoe hoe hoes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do reindeer have that no other animals have?",
    "answer": "Baby reindeer."
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of potato chip is Santa’s favorite?",
    "answer": "Crisp Pringles."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Santa’s favorite Olympic event?",
    "answer": "North Pole-vault."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do reindeer tell such good stories?",
    "answer": "Because they all have tails."
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you make a slow reindeer fast?",
    "answer": "You don’t feed it."
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the best thing to put into a Christmas pie?",
    "answer": "Your teeth."
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you find reindeer?",
    "answer": "Depends where you left them."
  },
  {
    "question": "Noah: I thought we had two turkeys when we left?",
    "answer": "Noah’s Wife: Well, it is Christmas."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the bald man say when he got a comb for Christmas?",
    "answer": "Thanks, I’ll never part with it."
  },
  {
    "question": "If a reindeer lost his tail, where would it go for a new one?",
    "answer": "A re-tail shop."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call it when Santa takes a break from delivering presents?",
    "answer": "Santa pause."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call it when Kris Kringle claps his hands?",
    "answer": "Santapplause."
  }
]